https://lifestyleaustralia.com.au/privacy-policy/

Branded Solutions CorporateRetail BrandsEvent MerchandiseUnionsTourismMiningWorkwearEco-FriendlySportwearGolf ProductsAbout UsShowcaseBlogGET A QUOTE
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThis following sets forth the Privacy Policy for the Lifestyle Australia website, www.lifestyleaustralia.com.au and was created in line with the existing privacy principles and the revised Privacy Amendment (Enhancing Privacy Protection) Act 2012 that takes effect March 12 2014.What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you visit our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter: your name, your business name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.What do we use for your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalise your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).To improve customer service (your information helps us to effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site featureTo send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, unless you subscribe to our marketing emails.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future marketing emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal informaiton when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server.  All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorised with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials etc) will not be stored on servers.Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or services providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping card, understand and save your preference for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. Third party vendors such as Google or DoubleClick may place cookies on your computer to track your browsing habits on Lifestyle Australia to serve ads to you in the future relating to products and pages you have looked at on our site.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings.  Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service on 07 3386 3600.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties (e.g freight companies) who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property or safety.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have seperate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 25th November 2013.Your rightsYou have the right to access personal information at Lifestyle Australia if you believe it is erroneous by contacting the General Manager via the means below. For security reasons, Lifestyle Australia reserves the rights to reasonably control the process and timing of access to your information on a per request basis.Any complaint regarding a perceived breach of the Australian Privacy Principles should be directed in the first instance in writing to the General Manager at Lifestyle Australia who will respond within the allowed timeframe (30days). Should the complaint not be dealt with to your satisfaction you may escalate the complaint to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner (refer www.oaic.gov.au).Contacting UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us by any of the following means during business hours Monday to Friday.Call: 07 3386 3600Post: Att Privacy PolicyLifestyle Australia 10 Access Avenue Yatala, QLD, 4207Email: privacy-policy@lifestyleaustralia.com.au
